diabetescare.net 2010-02-06

# DiabetesCare.Net - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers the Web site DiabetesCare.net and is effective as of December 10, 2007.

DiabetesCare.net is to be used for informational purposes and provides access to website tools, logs, and journals to assist in the self-management of the user`s health. It is not intended to serve as a substitute for advice from your health care provider. 

Information Collected

As part of standard Internet practice we collect the following information when you visit our site:

  * The IP address of the computer from which you accessed DiabetesCare.net;
  * Browser/operating system used to access our site;
  * A timestamp of when you visited our site;
  * Web addresses of websites from which you linked to our site;
  * Pages you visit within DiabetesCare.net and FoodSciences.com; and
  * Links made to other websites through this site.

This information collected may be used to improve the content of DiabetesCare.net, to notify visitors about updates to our website, and for statistical analysis using standard third-party software programs to create summary statistics. The statistics are used for the purpose of determining what information is of most and least interest to all visitors and identifying system performance or problem areas. 

Any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide will be collected. Personally identifiable information may include website preferences, an email address, street address, or any other information you submit via a website when completing a form or survey online. 

Cookies

The Self-Care Tools section of DiabetesCare.net uses cookies to store user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, and customize Web page content on visitors` browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

Public Disclosure

With the exception that DiabetesCare.net may provide your name and email address to an appropriate service provider, any personally identifiable information collected online will not be shared with other organizations or for any commercial purposes except where you have given us permission or where the information is public information. 

Access to User Profiles 

Any personally identifiable information you enter in a user profile will be open and accessible to you for review or modify. 

Choice

You may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e., tools, logs, journals, emails). Your choice to not participate will have no effect on your ability to view information on the main part of the site. In order to access certain parts of our site, including but not limited to MyCare Tools, Forums, and our newsletter service, [users must first register](http://diabetescare.net/forum/registration_rules.asp?FID=0). 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line, you may receive occasional mailings from us with information on products and services or upcoming events. During the registration process, you will have the opportunity to choose to receive information by e-mail, postal mail, or both. If you do not want to receive such mailings or e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by deselecting the appropriate box when you register or by clicking on My Profile. You may also send an e-mail with "unsubscribe" in the subject to [contact@DiabetesCare.net](mailto:contact@DiabetesCare.net) stating that you no longer wish to receive e-mails and/or postal mail from DiabetesCare.net. 

Security

If you register to access the DiabetesCare.net self-care tools, you will be asked to create a password which will be required in order to access or submit personal information. You should not divulge your password to anyone. DiabetesCare.net will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. When you are finished with sites that are password protected, you should exit the page. 

Link Disclaimer 

DiabetesCare.net contains links to other websites. A link does not constitute an endorsement of content, viewpoint, policies, products or services of that website. Once you link to another website, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that website, including but not limited to its privacy policy. 

Changes to Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. In addition, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

Information Disclaimer

While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current and reliable information we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Therefore, DiabetesCare.net, Food Sciences Corporation, its employees, officers and agencies expressly deny any warranty of the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance upon the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Any person who relies upon such information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk. 

**Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.**

COPYRIGHT NOTICE© 1999-2010, PriorityDigital.com Prepared for: DiabetesCare.Net. All rights reserved.
